[{"answer": "Well, what I've learned growing up in our family is that, you know, integrity is everything.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "And I knew then I had a deal because Howard, the Buffett handshake means a lot, right?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "We -- Well, I don't -- it's not the higher percentage but of the ones I've made deals with, I've decided that their handshake is good.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "How many men in the world or women, people you do business with, do you trust personally for big a deal on the strength of a handshake, percentage- wise?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Regardless of any piece of paper.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Regardless of any bit of paper?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Yeah, I prefer to do business with people I like.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "And do you still prefer to do business with a handshake?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well both my grandfather and my father have been the most amazing role models that anyone could imagine.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "But let me ask you, HWB, what is the single best lesson you have learned from the elder Buffetts in your life, so far would you say?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Well, it's to look at stocks as part of the business rather than little things that bob up and down.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "So we've got plenty of tweets pouring in Jane Fagan Smith (ph) said what's the most important advice you've ever had about investing that you would impart to others?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "Well, I enjoyed them.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "Do you have to personally enjoy the stocks that you buy big in?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "So we used a major rock star writers, there was one request, anything Coca-Cola related?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "I'm a BlackBerry relic, I still hang on to the BlackBerry, it turns that HWB here has two BlackBerries?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, I don't throw anything away until I got it 20 or 25 years.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "How long have you had that one?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "I do it through my assistant.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "Do you use e-mail?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "I sent it to Jeff Wright at Microsoft and it ended up in court in Minneapolis court.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Who to?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Well, it's not so old.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Well, I have everything I want, you know, I'm happy.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "You're not into flashy things, are you really?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Yeah, and I started feeding candy and pie and all this ....", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "... the rent went down?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "No, not really.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "So it didn't work?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "It was a deal.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "... so that there was no wavering on your part?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "I would say it was dumb.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "It seems to me that the two incentives, one worked and one didn't would you regret the weight incentive that you laid down with your son?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "You know, I don't think I've ever done that.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Has he had the same criteria?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "That's true.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "All three of your children went to public schools?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Well, for one thing, if they combine their credits, we can get one degree and that's...", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "You don't seem to faze, why?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "No, you painted it that way.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Was he -- I don't want to use the word mean, but was he a little tight fisted, Howard, from the way you're painting this picture?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Yes, but he can figure out how those go on.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "But, you would only hear one side of the call?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "$34 billion.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 192, "question": "And how much did you pay?", "qSentId": 191}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Do you often make big mistakes?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "ARREN BUFFETT: Well, I bought a company in the mid 90's called Dexter Shoe and paid $400 million for it.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "What's been the one you think I should never have done that?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Would you agree with that, Warren?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, she is -- first of all, she did something, you had my dad saying earlier which is, she provided unconditional love to all three of us.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Tell me why?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "Well, I had a roll of windows in my room and, you know, I opened the window up, we had this greenhouse so I'd be careful climbing out because I don't want to go through the glass, but I got down and we had our charge account at the local hardware store about five blocks away and I went up there and I convinced the guy to let me charge a hasp lock, I had to buy a screw driver because I didn't have any tools and I get everything I needed and I crawled back up in and I locked her out.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "But not you Howard, what did you do?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "I think as it is, she probably got a kick out of it.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "How did you mother react?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "I slowly grew up and I wouldn't have otherwise.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "How did you change?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Sure, sure.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "Just to override, anything else you would write?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Well, to be frank it's been normal in a sense that we grew up in a normal house.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "I mean tell me about what is like growing up in this kind of family?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Well, I want them to be good citizens, good parents that the -- what the world would be better off because they were here.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Warren, what other the key values that you would like to see other people recognize in your children, your grandchildren, your family, your extended family?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Well, I'm not sure I can give you a great one.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "What is your definition of that?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I'm not sure where the time lock is.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "He says its thread bare and dust and has cobwebs, right Howard?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Well, the \"Forty Chances\" comes from actually my career farming.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 360, "question": "Howard tell me about this book \"Forty Chances\", why the title?", "qSentId": 359}, {"answer": "Well, one of the biggest things I've learned is -- I mean there's a lot of great organizations out there.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "How do you deal with that?", "qSentId": 377}, {"answer": "Well, he's offered in the premise as my other two children and that it's a (Gage) foundation so that all lives have equal value.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "What do you make of what he's achieved?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "I'm very proud of him.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Proud of him?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Unfortunately, that range is at a corporate.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Can you do any better on salary?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "We think the $0.25 a mile is pretty generous.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "What about mileage when I use my car, I mean gas ain't cheap, you know?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "I wouldn't say that, but nice thing about being mildly famous is that the worst you are the better people like it.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Warren Buffett negotiating with the gang on NBC's The Office that legendary attention to details, I'm met his family, one of the most influential in the world back now with the three generations of Buffetts, Warren, Howard G, and Howard W. Do you enjoy being an actor there, Warren, well you're quite good?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Oh, they come up with, you know, they say, \"Are you really?\"", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 414, "question": "What is do you think most people when they see you in the street recognize you, ask you?", "qSentId": 413}, {"answer": "Well, let's take a look.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "If I was to ask you that now, what would the answers be?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "I got this wallet for -- here's my.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Is this Edward (inaudible) on television before?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Probably about 20 years, maybe.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "How long have you had it first?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Here's my American express card from 1964.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "And what do you have in it?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "Yes, well it goes with my cell phone.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "That's the one you've had the whole time?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Well, I have a variety of cards, but there's a picture of the family.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "What other cards do you have?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "More than usual that ...", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "And how much cash?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "The resiliency of people.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Of all the places you've been, of all the issues you've dealt with, what is being the most powerful to you personally?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "I think that both parties should declare the debt limit as a political weapon of mass destruction which can't be use.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Seems like (inaudible) on air in CNN in three years there's going to be some crisis involving Washington, debt ceilings, shutdowns, how do we try and bring an end to all this and actually move forward for the benefit of the American economy and the American people?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "Terrific, terrific.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "What is the future for America Incorporated do you think?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Well you an multiply all the value but it's all going to plan.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Do you know how much you're worth?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "No I never met Frank Sinatra.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "Have you ever met Frank Sinatra before he died?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "I'm a fan.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "You're a fan?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Yes and you just (inaudible).", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "ORGAN: And you're a fan of the Ukulele?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "We had a lot of fun.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "A bit inundated with tweets, many of them say, these Buffett boys are a lot of fun aren't they?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "I've enjoyed it a lot.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "You don't do this kind of interview very often Warren, how do you enjoy the last hour?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "A teacher, teacher, yeah, well actually I'd like to remembered as the oldest man that ever lived, I'm sure that's with the (inaudible).", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "How would you like to be remembered?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "The time with my dad, some moment, any moment.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "Which moment would you choose?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Electric.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "William Shatner how are you?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "82.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Come on, how old are you?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "Well first of all.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 559, "question": "What is the secret to eternal youth, William Shatner?", "qSentId": 558}, {"answer": "All those lines I had to learn to, I swear allegiance, then I had to memorize that stuff.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "Why have you never become an American citizen?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "We don't know.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "Well what would you make of the whole, never mind all the debt standoff, what do you make of the ObamaCare dispute?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Fire them all and have a new election.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "How would Captain James T. Kirk run America right now if he was President?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Well it's not weird and strange.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "... it has to be mysterious and weird and strange?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "We are composed of all of it and we have to maintain control of those impulses that are negative.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "What's the simple answer?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "All the time.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Do you ever get highly emotional?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "About the album?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "No, the best journeys -- are when you don't know where you're going and you make the discovery as you go along from point to point.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Do you know where you're going?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "Well I felt transported by writing the lyrics and then when Billy Sherwood wove the music around my words and then we have these great musicians come in and play (inaudible).", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 621, "question": "When you're making this music?", "qSentId": 620}, {"answer": "Yes, there a number of residents that are walking around.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "Do you see people walking around?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "This -- it does look quite similar to disasters I have seen in the past just the sheer devastation and the debris everywhere.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "Have you ever seen anything like this?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "At this point, we're not getting any numbers at all.", "docId": "131108pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "Paula, any indication -- are you getting any numbers on the death toll?", "qSentId": 681}]